{
	"questions": [{
			"question": "What was Sergei Rachmaninoff's profession?",
			"answers": [
				"Painter",
				"Composer",
				"Scientist",
				"Actor"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "Where was Sergei Rachmaninoff born?",
			"answers": [
				"Germany",
				"USA",
				"Russia",
				"France"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of Rachmaninoff's most famous composition?",
			"answers": [
				"Moonlight Sonata",
				"Prelude in C-sharp minor",
				"The Nutcracker",
				"Symphony No. 5"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "What instrument did Rachmaninoff play?",
			"answers": [
				"Violin",
				"Piano",
				"Flute",
				"Drums"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},

		{
			"question": "In what year did Rachmaninoff emigrate to the United States?",
			"answers": [
				"1917",
				"1921",
				"1910",
				"1925"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the title of Rachmaninoff's first symphony?",
			"answers": [
				"The Bells",
				"Symphony No. 1",
				"Isle of the Dead",
				"Rhapsody on a Theme of Paganini"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the condition that Rachmaninoff was believed to have, which gave him an extraordinary reach at the piano?",
			"answers": [
				"Marfan Syndrome",
				"Ehlers-Danlos Syndrome",
				"Arachnodactyly",
				"Osteogenesis Imperfecta"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "What was the name of the estate where Rachmaninoff was born?",
			"answers": [
				"Ivanovka",
				"Oneg",
				"Semyonovo",
				"Novgorod"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"level": "hard",
			"items": [{
					"question": "What was the name of Rachmaninoff's cousin who was also a famous composer?",
					"answers": [
						"Alexander Scriabin",
						"Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov",
						"Alexander Glazunov",
						"Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky"
					],
					"correctAnswerIndex": 0
				},
				{
					"question": "What is the name of the piece that Rachmaninoff composed for his graduation from the Moscow Conservatory?",
					"answers": [
						"Piano Concerto No. 1",
						"Rhapsody on a Theme of Paganini",
						"Aleko",
						"Symphony No. 2"
					],
					"correctAnswerIndex": 2
				},
				{
					"question": "Who was the conductor at the disastrous premiere of Rachmaninoff's Symphony No. 1?",
					"answers": [
						"Alexander Glazunov",
						"Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov",
						"Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky",
						"Sergei Rachmaninoff"
					],
					"correctAnswerIndex": 0
				},
				{
					"question": "What was the name of Rachmaninoff's wife?",
					"answers": [
						"Natalia Satina",
						"Anna Yesipova",
						"Elisaveta Petrovna",
						"Maria Siloti"
					],
					"correctAnswerIndex": 0
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "What was the name of the hypnotherapist who helped Rachmaninoff overcome his depression and writer's block?",
			"answers": [
				"Nikolai Dahl",
				"Sigmund Freud",
				"Carl Jung",
				"Ivan Pavlov"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the choral symphony composed by Rachmaninoff, based on a poem by Edgar Allan Poe?",
			"answers": [
				"The Bells",
				"The Raven",
				"Annabel Lee",
				"The Fall of the House of Usher"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the piece that Rachmaninoff considered his best composition?",
			"answers": [
				"Symphony No. 2",
				"Piano Concerto No. 3",
				"Rhapsody on a Theme of Paganini",
				"All-Night Vigil"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 3
		},
		{
			"question": "What was the last piece of music Rachmaninoff played in public before his death?",
			"answers": [
				"Piano Concerto No. 2",
				"Prelude in C-sharp minor",
				"Rhapsody on a Theme of Paganini",
				"Piano Concerto No. 3"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		}
	]

}
